smskhan.com 2013-08-15

# Privacy Policy | SMSKHAN.COM

**Privacy policy**  is a statement or a legal document (privacy law) that discloses some or all of the ways a party gathers, uses, discloses and manages a customer or client’s data. Personal information can be anything that can be used to identify an individual, not limited to but including; name, address, date of birth, marital status, contact information, ID issue and expiry date, financial records, credit information, medical history, where you travel, and intentions to acquire goods and services. In the case of a business it is often a statement that declares a party’s policy on how it collects, stores, and releases personal information it collects. It informs the client what specific information is collected, and whether it is kept confidential, shared with partners, or sold to other firms or enterprises.

The four critical issues identified in Fair Information Principles are:

  * Notice – data collectors must disclose their information practices before collecting personal information from consumers
  * Choice – consumers must be given options with respect to whether and how personal information collected from them may be used for purposes beyond those for which the information was provided
  * Access – consumers should be able to view and contest the accuracy and completeness of data collected about them
  * Security – data collectors must take reasonable steps to assure that information collected from consumers is accurate and secure from unauthorized use.

In addition the Principles discuss the need for enforcement mechanisms to impose sanctions for non-compliance with fair information practices.

Hi our website www.smskhan.com uses (google analytics) to collect visitor data and analyze traffic on our site. Here we are describing this all because we collect the information of our user to analyze traffic on our site, not more than that. So our users feel free to use our smskhan.com site. This information helps us understand customer interests and helps us improve our website. When you visit our site, the pages that you look at, and a short text file called a cookie, are downloaded to your computer. A cookie is used to store small amounts of information. This information is collected for traffic analysis only. The cookie does not contain personal details. Depending on the browser that you use, you can set your preferences to block/ refuse cookies, and/ or notify you before they are placed. Google Analytics does not sell, give, or trade the statistics they store to any 3rd parties for data-mining or marketing purposes. Please visit www.google.com/analytics for their privacy policy. For further more details of Privacy Policy Please visit this Link : [www.google.com/analytics](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ "Google privacy policy")
